Guide to the Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance Periodicals Collection, 1962-1994 RL.00024
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- ALFA Periodicals Collection, 1972-1994, 47 boxes
  - Poverty Law Report / Klanwatch Intelligence Report (Montgomery, Ala.), 1982 February (Box 34)
  - Prime Time, 1977 August (Box 34)
  - Project Open Hand/Atlanta Digest, 1989 January-1992 (Box 34)
  - Puce Mongoose (Garwood, N.J.), 1975 September-1981 October (Box 34)
    [formerly: Lazette]
  - Pulse (Atlanta, Ga.), 1984 June-1985 January [?] (Box 34)
  - Purple Rage: Lesbian/Feminism/Revolution (New York, N.Y.), 1972 [?] (Box 34)
  - Purple Star (Ann Arbor, M.I.), 1971 (Box 34)
  - Q-Notes (Charlotte, N.C.) (Box 34)
  - Quash (New York, N.Y.), 1976 January-1983 January (Box 34)
  - Quilting Bee- Line (Atlanta, Ga.), 1989 April-1992 (Box 34)
  - Radiance (Oakland, Calif.), 1985-1989 [?] (Box 34)
  - Rag Times (Portland, Ore.), 1985 December-1987 January (Box 34)
  - RAT, 1970 October-1972 June (Box 34)
  - Reach Out: International Women's Newsletter (San Francisco, Calif.), 1991 November-1992 July [?] (Box 35)
  - Recon, 1984 February-[?] (Box 35)
  - Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights Newsletter, 1990, 1993 (Box 35)
  - Religious Coalition for Abortion: Common Ground - Different Planes, 1988 April-1991 (Box 35)
    [missing: 1989]
  - Reproductive Rights Newsletter (Chicago, Ill.), 1978-1984 (Box 35)
  - Resources, 1974 (Box 35)
  - RFD: A Country Journal for Gay Men, 1979-1981 (Box 35)
  - Richmond Lesbian Festival, 1986 June (Box 35)
  - Rites for Lesbian and Gay Liberation (Ontario, Canada), 1986 May-1988 June (Box 35)
  - Room of One's Own, 1985 April-1990 [?] (Box 35)
    [missing 1986-1989]
  - Rubyfruit Review (Tallahassee, Fla.), 1989 September-1990 December (Box 35)
  - Runes, 1978 October [?] (Box 35)
  - Sage: A Scholarly Journal on Black Women (Atlanta, Ga.), 1984-1990 (Box 35)
  - Sage - Femme, 1977 October [?] (Box 35)
  - Sage Woman: A Quarterly Magazine of Women's Spirituality (Santa Cruz, Calif.), 1988 (Box 35)
  - Saint Petersburg Women's Alliance (Saint Petersburg, Fla.), 1975 [?] (Box 35)
  - Salga: Southern Appalachian Lesbian and Gay Alliance Newsletter (Asheville, N.C.), 1989 [?] (Box 35)
  - Sandhill Monitor (Sandhill Farms) (Twin City, Ga.), 1991 August (Box 35)
  - SANE News (Middletown, Conn.), 1978 September-1980 February [?] (Box 35)
  - San Francisco Bay Area Gay and Lesbian Historical Society Newsletter (San Francisco, Calif.), 1987 September-1990 (Box 35)
  - San Jose (CA) Lesbian Feminist, 1976 December-1976 May (Box 35)
  - Santa Fe Women's Community Magazine (Santa Fe, N.M.), 1973 (Box 35)
  - Sappho (London, England), dates uknown (Box 35)
  - Scene, The (San Diego, Calif.), 1987 June (Box 35)
  - Schlabber Laz (Germany), 1990 [?] (Box 35)
  - Seattle Gay News (Seattle, Wash.), 1977 March-1982 December (Box 35)
    [missing: 1980-1981]
  - Second Stone: National Newspaper for Gay and Lesbian Christians (New Orleans, La.), 1989 March-1991 June (Box 35)
  - Second Wave, The (Cambridge, Mass.), circa 1971-1976 (Box 35)
  - Second Wave, The (Saskatchewan), 1987 October-1987 December (Box 36)
  - Secret Storm, 1975 March (Box 36)
  - Sexual Abstinence News (Houston, Texas), 1987 March (Box 36)
  - Sexual Law Reporter (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1975 June-1978 December (Box 36)
  - She Magazine (Hollywood, Fla.), 1979 November-1981 July [?] (Box 36)
  - She, 1973 April (Box 36)
  - Short Mountain Goatzette (Liberty, Tenn.), 1985 (Box 36)
  - Shrew, 1972 April-1972 June (Box 36)
  - Sinister Wisdom (Charlotte, N.C. and Amherst, Mass.), 1976 July-1980 (Box 36)
  - Sissies in Struggle (New Orleans, La.), 1978 March (Box 36)
  - Sister, 1973 April (Box 36)
  - Sibyl - Child (Hyattsville, Md.), 1978 September-1981 July [?] (Box 36)
  - Signal (Boston, Mass.), 1977 January (Box 36)
  - Signal (Georgia State University) (Atlanta, Ga.), 1984 November (Box 36)
  - Single Parent News, 1976 (Box 36)
  - Sister Advocate (Oklahoma City, Okla.), 1978-1979 [?] (Box 36)
  - Sister Courage (Allston, Mass.), 1976 May-1978 May (Box 36)
  - Sisterhood (University of Michigan) (Ann Arbor, Mich.), 1972 November (Box 36)
  - Spoiler Lode (Albequerque, N.M.), 1985 February-1985 July [?] (Box 36)
  - Sister Namibia, 1989 July (Box 36)
  - Sisters (San Francisco, Calif.), 1971 November-1975 (Box 36)
  - Sisters Newsletter (Atlanta, Ga.), 1985 August-1985 September (Box 36)
  - Sistership (Australia), 1988 June (Box 36)
  - Sister Source (Chicago, Ill.), 1981 August-1982 December (Box 36)
  - Sisterspace - Black Women's Health Project / Women's Heath Concerns Committee (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1982 September-1984 June [?] (Box 36)
  - Sisters United (Galena, Kan.), 1979 September-1988 (Box 37)
    [missing: 1984-1985]
  - Skip Two Periods (Roanoke, Va.), 1985 June (Box 37)
  - Socialist Feminist Reporter (Seattle, Wash.), 1981 May (Box 37)
  - Socialist Woman (London, England), 1971 March-1972 (Box 37)
  - Society of American Archivists - Lesbian and Gay Archives Roundtable - Newsletter, 1991 January (Box 37)
  - Sojourner, 1981 April-1981 May (Box 37)
  - Sojourner: New England Women's Journal of News, Opinions, and the Acts (Boston / Cambridge, Mass.), 1980 June-1993 August [?] (Box 37-38)
  - Something About the Women, 1980 October-1990 December (Box 38)
  - So's Your Old Lady (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1974-1977 July (Box 38)
  - Soundstage South (Tallahassee, Fla.), 1984 (Box 38)
  - Sourceline (Anchorage, Ark.), 1978 February-1981 June (Box 38)
  - Les Sourcieres (Montreal, Quebec), 1982 August [?] (Box 38)
  - South Carolina Gay and Lesbian Pride March, 1991 May [?] (Box 38)
  - Southeastern Arts, Media, and Education Project, Inc., 1988 January (Box 38)
  - Southeastern Women's Studies Association News, 1978 January-1991 November (Box 38)
  - Southern Coalition Report on Jails and Prisons (Nashville, Tenn.), 1984-1985 March [?] (Box 38)
  - Southern Exposure (Durham, N.C.), 1983 July-1988 (Box 38)
    [missing: 1984-1987]
  - Southern Feminist (Athens, Ga.), 1985 November -1985 December (Box 38)
  - Southern Feminist Connection (Winston Salem, N.C.), 1975 May-1976 March [?] (Box 38)
  - Southern Gay Liberator, 1971 [?] (Box 38)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center: Klanwatch (Montgomery, Ala.), 1981 July (Box 38)
  - Southern Struggle (Atlanta, Ga.), 1981 March [?] (Box 38)
  - Southern Voice (Atlanta, Ga.), 1988 March-[?] (Box 38-40)
  - Southwind: A Journal of Holistic Living, 1979 June (Box 40)
  - Spare Rib (London, England), 1985 June-1986 July (Box 40)
    [also: 1975 May]
  - Spartan Woman, The (Marietta, Ga.), 1981 October-1983 October (Box 40)
  - S.P.A.Z.M (Berkeley, Calif.), 1969 December (Box 40)
  - Spectre, 1971 May-1972 February (Box 40)
  - Spectrum (Tallahassee, Fla.), 1982 May-1986 July (Box 40)
  - Spelman Messenger (Atlanta, Ga.), 1981 (Box 40)
  - Spinster Haven, 1992 (Box 40)
  - Spiral Wimmin's Land Collective (Monticello, Ky.), 1980-1981 (Box 40)
  - Spokeswoman, The (Chicago, Ill.), 1970 June-1981 December (Box 40)
  - Spokeswoman, The (Toronto, Ontario), 1972 (Box 41)
  - Sportswoman, The, 1973-1974 October (Box 41)
  - STEHEKIN (Marietta, Ga.), 1983 February [?] (Box 41)
  - Stonewall Report, 1975-1976 August (Box 41)
  - Storm, The (New York, N.Y.), 1978 (Box 41)
  - Struggle (Sacramento, Calif.), 1977 August (Box 41)
  - Sunset, 1982 April (Box 41)
  - Supporters of Silkwood (Washington, D.C.), 1978 May (Box 41)
  - Susan Saxe Defense Committee News (West Somerville, Mass.), 1977 February-[?] (Box 41)
  - Taking Control, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Talisman - Hunter College, 1986 (Box 41)
  - Tallahassee Area Women's Network (TAWN) Newsletter, 1988 September-1994 June (Box 41)
  - Tallahassee Feminist Women's Health Center, 1980 April (Box 41)
  - Tallahassee, Florida Gay Central (Tallahassee, Fla.), 1977 September-1977 December (Box 41)
  - Tallahassee Women's Center Newsletter, 1973 May-1974 February (Box 41)
  - Tapestry- Womin's Outreach Network (W.O.N) (Missoula, Mont.), 1984 (Box 41)
  - Telewoman (Pennsylvania), 1980 October-1986 January (Box 41)
  - Thesmophoria (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1979 November-1991 [?] (Box 41)
  - Thirteenth Moon, dates unknown (Box 41)
  - This Is It (Athens, Ga.), 1982 March-1982 April (Box 41)
  - This Month In Mississippi (Jackson, Miss.), 1989 April (Box 41)
  - Through The Looking Glass (Seattle, Wash.), 1977 January-1987 (Box 41)
  - Through The Looking Glass (Pennsylvania), dates uknown (Box 41)
  - Tie Line (Lake Hiawatha, N.J.), 1987 November-1988 February (Box 42)
  - Times They Are A Changin' (Washington, D.C.), 1975 April (Box 42)
  - Tits and Clits Comix (Laguna Beach, Calif.), 1983 March [?] (Box 42)
  - T.L.C Newsletter, 1994 June (Box 42)
  - Toads, 1975 June (Box 42)
  - Tribune: A Women and Development Quarterly (New York, N.Y.), 1983 (Box 42)
  - Triple Jeopardy, 1974 March-1974 April (Box 42)
  - Triumph in 1986 (San Francisco, Calif.), 1985 September (Box 42)
  - True Colors, 1993 (Box 42)
  - Tracks, 1984 August (Box 42)
  - Tradeswomen: A Quarterly Magazine for Women in Blue-Collar Work, 1985-1986 (Box 42)
  - Travel-ons, Sylstereo International, Limited (New York, N.Y.), 1987-1988 (Box 42)
  - Travel Talk - Fountain Institution for Women (Rego Park, N.Y.), 1987-1988 (Box 42)
  - Tribad (New York, N.Y.), 1978 March-1979 April (Box 42)
  - Trumpet, The (Atlanta, Ga.), 1980 April-1983 December (Box 42)
  - Tulsa Oklahomans For Human Rights (TOHR Reported) (Tulsa, Okla.), 1987 September -1990 September (Box 42)
  - Tuscaloosa Lesbian Coalition Newsletter (Tuscaloosa, Ala.), 1989 July-1994 June (Box 42)
  - Twilight Times (Atlanta, Ga.), 1981 April (Box 42)
  - Twin Cities Gaze (Minneapolis/St. Paul, Minn. [?]), 1987 December (Box 42)
  - 212 (NYC), 1983 August (Box 42)
  - Unicorn (Boston, Mass.), 1981 (Box 42)
  - Union W.A.G.E., 1977 November [?] (Box 42)
  - University Y.W.C.A. (Honolulu, Hawaii), 1977 October-1986 (Box 42)
  - Unitarian Universalist Lesbian and Gay Community Newsletter (Atlanta, Ga.), 1981 November-1986 February (Box 42)
    [missing: 1983-1985]
  - Unitarian Universalist Lesbian/Gay World, 1981 December (Box 42)
  - United Sisters (U.S.), dates uknown (Box 42)
  - Unlimited, The (Fayetteville, Ark.), 1989 September (Box 42)
  - Update (Houston, Texas), 1981-1982 (Box 42)
  - Up From Under (New York, N.Y.), 1970 May-1973 (Box 42)
  - Valley Women's Union (Northampton, Mass.), 1975 December-1982 October (Box 42)
    [missing: 1976-1981]
  - Virago (Columbia, S.C.), 1991 July-1991 November (Box 42)
  - Visibilities (New York, N.Y.), 1988 July-1991 October (Box 42)
  - Visible, (We Are) (Mendocino, California), 1990 July-1993 April (Box 42)
  - Vital Signs, 1990 (Box 42)
  - Voix, 1976 September (Box 42)
  - Wages for Housework Campaign Bulletin (Toronto, Ontario), 1979-1981 (Box 42)
    [missing: 1980]
  - War Resistors League - Southeast (Durham, N.C.), 1981-1985 (Box 42)
  - Washington Area and Women's Center News (Washington, D.C.), 1975 September-1977 August (Box 42)
  - Washington Area Women's Center News (Washington, D.C.), 1975 Septebmer-1977 August (Box 42)
  - Water: An Occasional Resource, 1987 December-1991 (Box 42)
    [missing: 1988-1990]
  - Waterwheel: A Quarterly Newsletter of the Women's Alliance for Theology, Ethics, and Ritual, 1988-1992 (Box 42)
  - Wavelength (Seattle, Wash.), 1986-1992 (Box 42)
  - Web of Crones, A (Hornby Island, British Columbia), 1987-1988 [?] (Box 42)
  - We the Women (Atlanta, Ga.), 1982-1985 (Box 42)
    [missing: 1983-1984]
  - Wellesley College Center for Research on Women Research Report (Wellesley, Mass.), 1989-1990 (Box 42)
  - Wellspring, The (Colorado Springs, Colo.), 1978 July (Box 42)
  - West Coast Lesbian Collections "In the Life" (Oakland, Calif.), 1982-1984 (Box 42)
  - What She Wants, 1974 April (Box 42)
  - W.H.I.S.P.E.R. (Woman Hurt In Systems of Prostitution Engaged in Revolt) (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1986-1993 (Box 42)
  - Whole Woman Catalog, The, 1971 (Box 42)
  - WICCE (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1974-1975 (Box 43)
  - Wimmin of the Earth Bonding: W.E.B. Newsletter (Grand Rapids, Miss), 1982-1983 [?] (Box 43)
  - Win Peace and Freedom Thru Nonviolent Action, 1975 May (Box 43)
  - Windy City Times, 1991 January-1991 July [?] (Box 43)
  - Wisconsin Womyn's Land Newsletter, 1978 August (Box 43)
  - Wishing Well (Norato, Calif.), 1978-1982 (Box 43)
  - Woman News (New York, N.Y.), 1985 March-1991 March (Box 43)
  - Woman (Kalamazoo, Mich.), 1973 February (Box 43)
  - Woman Activist, The (Falls Church, Va.), 1979 March (Box 43)
  - Woman Becoming (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1972 December-1973 July (Box 43)
  - Womankind (Indianapolis, Ind.), 1981 [?] (Box 43)
  - Women of Power (Cambridge, Mass.), 1988 (Box 43)
  - Woman Power, 1973 January-1973 July (Box 43)
  - Woman Rising (Phoenix, Ariz.), 1976 (Box 43)
  - Woman's City Country Chronicle (Murfreesboro, Tenn.), 1982 August-1983 January (Box 43)
  - Woman's Network Views, 1985 June-1985 July (Box 43)
  - Womansight (Dallas, Texas), 1980 June-1981 October (Box 43)
  - Women's Journal Advocate, 1983 June-1984 November (Box 43)
  - Woman Spirit (Wolf Creek, Ore.), 1974-1984 (Box 44)
  - Woman's Place, A (Atlanta, Ga.), 1981 April-1983 August (Box 44)
  - Women's Way, 1994 [?] (Box 44)
  - Woman's Word (Athens, Ga.), 1977 July-1978 July (Box 44)
  - Woman's World (New York, N.Y.), 1971 July-1972 September (Box 44)
  - Woman Write - Penn State, 1980 (Box 44)
  - Women: A Journal of Liberation (Baltimore, Md.), 1969-1983 [?] (Box 44-45)
  - Women Against Pornography News Report (New York, N.Y.), 1980 December-1984 (Box 45)
  - Women and Film (Berkeley, Calif.), dates unknown (Box 45)
  - Women and Health Haworth Press, 1987 (Box 45)
  - Women and Performance: A Journal of Feminist Theory (New York, N.Y.), 1985 January [?] (Box 45)
  - Women and Recovery, 1992 February (Box 45)
  - Women and Revolution (New York, N.Y.), 1983 (Box 45)
  - Women in Kahoots, 1991 June-1994 March (Box 45)
  - Women in Libraries (Fairfax, Va.), 1982 June-1985 September (Box 45)
  - Women in Motion, 1972 September (Box 45)
  - Women In the Country (Flint, Mich.), 1978 February-1978 April (Box 45)
  - Women Library Workers, 1976 April-1983 September (Box 45)
    [missing: 1977-1979, 1982]
  - Women of Color News, 1984 January-1984 October (Box 45)
  - Women of Wisdom (Atlanta, Ga.), 1988 December-1993 June (Box 45)
  - Women Organizing, 1980 April (Box 45)
  - Women Oughta Know (Cupertino, Calif.), 1992 January-1991 March (Box 45)
  - Women's Alternatives Community Center Newsletter (Hempstead, N.Y.), 1988 March-1994 August (Box 45)
  - Women's Alternative Times (Austin, Texas), 1990 March-1990 September [?] (Box 45)
  - Women's Caucus Newsletter (Amherst, Mass.), 1973 April (Box 45)
  - Women's Coalition for Nairobi, 1985 July (Box 45)
  - Weal Washington Report (Washington, D.C.), 1973 May-1978 October (Box 45)
  - Women's Exchange Programme International Wed International News Bulletin, 1989 February-1994 (Box 45)
  - Women's Free Express (Nashville, Tenn.), 1974 March-1974 September (Box 45)
  - Women's Information Centre Newsletter, 1975 February-1976 March (Box 45)
  - Women's Institute of the Southeast (Atlanta, Ga.), 1982 November-1983 September [?] (Box 45)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1985 September-1985 October (Box 45)
  - Women's Issues News (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1978-1980 (Box 45)
  - Women's Liberation, 1970-1971 (Box 46)
  - Women's Monthly, The (Albany, N.Y.), 1980 November-1981 June (Box 46)
  - Women's National Abortion Action Coalition, 1972 October-1973 March (Box 46)
  - Women's Network, 1977 December (Box 46)
  - Women's Page, The, dates uknown (Box 46)
  - Women's Rights Law Reporter, 1971 July-1972 (Box 46)
  - Women's Rights Report, 1980 March-1980 October (Box 46)
  - Women's Street Theater, The, date uknown (Box 46)
  - Women's Studies Abstracts, 1972 -1973 (Box 46)
  - Women's Studies Newsletter, 1972-1980 (Box 46)
    [missing: 1973-1974, 1976-1979]
  - Women's Times, 1986 November-1990 March (Box 46)
  - Women's Voice (Detroit, Mich.), 1983 November (Box 46)
  - Women's Voice of Greater Hartford (Hartford, Conn.), 1972 December (Box 46)
  - Women's Washington Representative, 1977 May (Box 46)
  - Women's Words (Norwalk, Conn.), 1985 February (Box 46)
  - Women Today (Washington, D.C.), 1977 January-1977 May, 1980 July (Box 46)
  - Women Wise (Concord, N.H.), 1985-1989 (Box 46)
  - Women Writing Newsletter (Newfield, N.Y.), dates unknown (Box 46)
  - Womin Energy (Lexington, Ky.), 1977 November-1981 May [?] (Box 46)
  - Womynews (Asheville, N.C.), 1982 November (Box 46)
  - Womyn Lovers (Oakland, Calif.), 1981-1983 [?] (Box 46)
  - Womyn Space (Houston, Texas), 1985 March-1992 September [?] (Box 46)
  - Womyn Together (Asheville, N.C.), 1979 March-1986 February [?] (Box 46)
  - Womyn's Words (Saint Petersburg, Fla.), 1983 June-1994 May (Box 46)
    [Formerly: Women's Words]
  - Woods Women News, 1987-1994 [?] (Box 47)
  - Working Mother: The Voice of Mothers and Children's Liberation (New York), 1971-1973 [?] (Box 47)
  - Working Women Newsletter (Cleveland, Ohio), 1980 [?] (Box 47)
  - World Congress Digest, 1990 (Box 47)
  - Wree-view of Women, The, 1980, 1985 (Box 47)
    [includes 1980 January statement on draft of women]
  - WRFG (Atlanta, Ga.), 1981 April-1986 September (Box 47)
  - YWCAction (Atlanta, Ga.), 1974-1980 (Box 47)
  - Zeta Magazine (Boston, Mass.), 1988 [?] (Box 47)